Downloaded @ subs4free.club
I want her to know one thing.
I was a bad guy.
A very bad man
in the this life.
I learned not to
believe in anyone.
I lost faith in humanity.
I've decided I want doing
in life.
A good thing in my
life before he died.
Even die while doing it.
I also have to do the same.
John, come in.
As always, I am very
grateful he has to.
Sit down please.
He has a problem.
Not when he called me there
is also the problem that star.
Karma, the Afghans.
He is trying to steal technology
to sell on the black market.
News scout said he Accommodation
is in Pakistan.
He is very smart, and
carefully protected.
A party who has
called you hire me?
It is a new partner.
A new partner you?
A very special unit
on this world, John.
And I only call you when
I know new only he can.
I can do very
gentle, I know, not noisy.
But if you put me in death,
I will seek to kill him.
I just need you to know that.
Listen up,
How mean he accepted right?
That is, I will check him.
And... if he is
right a bad guy,
he is an enemy of United
States of America.
Or is he really liked the terrorist
activity or something.
I will make him disappear.
Hi Dai Long.
- Flights how?
- Long, but very nice to meet you.
Everything was arranged, everything
needed for the campaign.
I just ordered it.
I play you?
- Good.
- Rock and Roll.
I arranged the furniture here.
Odessa, Ukraine.
Oh, lovely sister.
I like you too.
Look.
Come here, come here honey.
How many names?
Unknown, only 2 cars go on.
Prepared under my command.
Diana, as always.
Go on.
She said men have
taste how and know.
The boss wants to
do more than that.
We can talk, in fact, I'm
going to pay my funeral.
And he was very close to
his uncle they of Karma.
We have many contacts. I think
he wanted to see the boss uncle.
Note that bored Karma ago.
Like us.
We will soon invite.
Karma is
becoming Recent tampering.
And you know what
I mean and know.
Maybe tonight should meet
worm Afghani this a bit.
Feel free to take you.
I bought them from Diana
that she quite fluent.
You should talk to her.
Girls gu is a breeze.
Actually I do not like
the type of guy the like.
Recently his
attention more than that.
I do not talk to anyone.
I do not work for him. The
only way for him to get paid.
As I. And I do what
the hell I prefer.
Like boss. How the hell do
that attention be?
Bosses have many concerns,
he did not want to risk.
Do not worry, you think
I'm stupid really make?
I'm smarter than any name
do you see that hook.
Sure.
But he should know them Americans
are not happy there.
Mother Shelf us Americans,
Need hell to pay attention...
- The evening of fun.
- Go away!
I will come in when
we go out, unobserved,
as neat.
What party?
A lady must be staying in the
house this would be a pity.
Maybe I'll go
for a little walk.
Fresh air, smoking
a cigarette.
Carry out only.
Hey, that team?
As a name under the stairs.
What the hell he's doing...
My protector, What the hell...
Calm down, calm go buddy.
Listen, I...
My family is very wealthy,
he was What? What is it?
Where do your
family that amount?
This is the business of
my family, not my story.
It's a hassle, and his mouth even
more complicated, it is a burden.
And I think this is a
joke, huh? Variable Dum go.
No, not about him where.
It is about my boss.
British American men, huh?
For girls go live.
- The task is finished now?
- It is done, everything on the list.
Neat.
Need to exchange something?
I'm waiting for
compensation only.
Time has changed little.
What does it mean?
The shipment was delayed,
So we have to wait.
But when the goods would
tell him right away, John.
Now, wait I say go, then go.
Just as the
invisible, reclusive.
Clear.
We delayed.
So we on now?
The problem is that the
task is not done yet.
I suggest we to
shop Daniel, taking a li,
relax, hiding. Do
ghosts, always been ghosts.
And... we will be out
of here soon enough.
Are.
Give me a vodka and
li Johnie Walker.
There are right.
And some cigar.
Hello.
What?
Sorry I'm late.
I have a massage.
Slightly longer
than I thought a bit.
He went massage
seems happy anyway.
Let me know, little
brother here great massage.
In Hong Kong, where earn?
I do not know, in the past
in Hong Kong it is also fun.
Let me ask you one thing,
3 years ago
I'm walking.
The boss he stepped
out of the car and...
There's a girl in the car.
Bad guys jump out
to kill his boss.
He looked at me like,
she will die in
it. I knew that look.
So I made a few hand
bad things with them.
And we gone
forever, he was saved.
And I know he is a godfather stunned
in HK, which is his boss.
He asked him to
follow me For years
as a gift for
debt that he thought
that he owed me.
That was 3 years ago.
I still do not get rid of him.
Me in Macau for it?
Yes.
He saved my life
in such cases.
It's just something
we have to do.
Since then we have not
only is the repayment grace.
He became my brothers.
We regarded each
other as brothers.
Where I live
there is a saying.
This means that when night
falls, and one brother.
I will be with him, no
need to say anything.
As an oath,
something immutable,
I will do everything
to honor it.
That's our job, but.
We live
together, we die together.
We go together, and
fight together.
Yes.
Can li.
Having just mentioned.
Please allow offline
University Long.
Hello Baby.
- Do you?
- Athletic, but he?
- Health, what you name?
- Angela.
Angela, or so, he is Chi.
Hi Chi.
Just run away and
then I'll catch you.
Look at her go.
Help me.
Help!
Please, help me.
Help! Please, they will kill
me, please, if you please.
- Please take that.
- It's not your eyebrows.
Why do people work on?
Do not stick to it.
They will kill me!
That's enough. Come on.
Hearing her say and
know, leave her alone.
What to do? Drop her off.
- About alone.
- Split.
- No one knows us.
- Good.
Wait wait.
Please, please help me.
What are you doing in here?
I do not know where to go.
They will kill me.
Then go quickly, and
get out of here.
Go away.
- Get out of here.
- No...
Listen up,
I did everything
the way I can then.
Please, out of the
car, We will come here soon.
No, I know he is a very
powerful people.
I know what happened to me
not concerned, I understand.
But he does not like them.
Please go.
- You sure do not like you?
- Yeah, I do not like them.
- Bet she lives in me?
- Yes.
Yeah, I do not like them.
US Embassy.
Karma was killed tonight, the
crowd guards again, no one saw anything.
I will do this?
What do u? He is a burden.
Know why not? None know
anything about it so...
- In other words we go again.
- Good evening.
She has a bright
evening too, huh.
Thank you, and I have
4 messages for him,
And an appointment.
- Thank you.
- Nothing.
There are other stories, some names
are beaten in the restaurant Daniel,
We're chasing a girl, Sure
related to the killer.
What girl?
Well, she went to...
our friends.
Damn.
They still alive?
He let them live
certain purposes.
- Take the hospital yet?
- Then.
Only one hand
cause story there?
I have investigated,
the Asian guy,
but the girl to accompany him.
This.
He brought her to here?
Yeah, I'm in
trouble, I broke the rules.
Listen, there are a lot of
eyes see you in the tavern,
Now this girl again, do not know Who
wants to kill her, too dangerous.
I just do not want
to us kill her alone.
Okay, what do you plan?
We will send her some money
and drop her somewhere safe
Then you and me out of here.
Yeah, we'll need
someone to help you.
I have a friend Russia.
I will call him to see if
What guns are not helping.
Bothered her since we heard, we need
to know to help you in this matter.
He will not want to know.
Better that we should
know, to help her.
If she wants to live,
please Tell us, if not
we will ignore. She
would say things
and will listen to
everything I told her to do.
They will kill you.
Oh no.
What we do here Chi?
I panic here.
Should I run it?
Why do not always matter.
Maybe I just came out here
to care for a baby
in the rich family.
3 years.
3 years uninterrupted!
John, look at this.
She wanted to say something
about them? It's in her coat.
It would be stupid
if we revealed
but do not know
what is happening, so...
I do not know, I'm thinking,
She needs some money
and we outta here.
Unless she says
everything I think she left unsaid.
Look, there is
one page 2 names.
Nadia and Sofia.
Who is Sofia?
Sofia is my sister.
And he hit her
death with the tube.
Do you know who he is,
and He put her to anywhere?
It was very strange at
the beginning, is not?
A girl came to
us before and...
And then they came.
And they took me away and
Sofia 2 girls together again.
Please.
And they took us to a bar and
go to a room and
behold outrageous.
And he was there.
Wear a mask.
Speak loudly yet!
There are those who are
very sick in the world,
okay?
but if we have enough money,
they will never get caught.
Look at her go.
Must survivors out here.
You want to see me, huh?
Nadia, take the camera
away, Nadia ran away!
Just run away and
I will find you.
Bitch.
But you have to pay
the price for this.
Where it is not
going away, catch it.
Do you know who he is
and where they are not?
I do not know.
I just know that we have
relations very strong here.
And he,
he has hit our
people at the bar.
Nadia.
I want her to know one thing.
I was a bad guy.
A very bad man in my life.
I've learned not
to believe anyone.
I have lost faith in humanity.
I believe that anyone who I
also want to play outside.
So I have decided
to do something
in life.
A good thing in this life.
Even if I must die doing it.
I also find this name.
I will find him
and I will kill him.
I need to do it
coming together.
He had a camera
and I had to get it.
He turned around
everything, everything he does.
I can show you where I hid it.
This,
or not at all.
Perhaps we have hired the
wrong person Afghani and tasks.
"We" it?
This story is by me, sir. I
hired the wrong person to do it.
Im going.
We need quickly settle this.
Call Van Horn travel.
He said what the hell?
Where no simple story.
Just jump on the bar
with 3 of my boys.
It seems that just as these
guys destructive gameplay alone.
Can you assure me that you
manage the people you do not?
I have a lot of people
to solve a lot of work.
All are smooth, cleanliness.
The arrest of a girl you
have, she belongs to me.
And you, please listen up.
I want to get her back.
John, why do not you say something
about the a girl that was saved?
That is not something
important.
It is important that story
Whom he had quarrel, He wanted
to know why and where she is?
Why pay attention
to her like that?
I think it is better that we do not
wonder much While we did wrong process.
Now let's bring that girl back
and everything running smoothly.
I think you can tell
me a little more time.
Found him then.
All right.
Then resolve to go away.
Make really neat to go. Alert
me to find the girl.
I went to see John.
This is Sergei.
We can say is my brother.
And you should believe him.
I believed him so many times.
We will need an outlet neat.
What is the time?
Within 24 hours.
Give me two hours.
We may have to against
the very best names.
Type them, we will be safe.
Go from here. That's our goal.
Two people go to the
address in the paper.
Learn about the
mastermind of this conspiracy.
Okay.
Careful.
Okay, Rock'n'Roll only.
Rock'n'Roll only.
My friend, I have no lighter?
Thank you.
I will ask a few
questions. Reply truth is life.
Lie was dying.
See?
He understand?
He spoke Russian.
That's why I carry
interpreters there.
What's in the house?
The girl.
What girl?
Traffickers.
The head is?
Stretch a little.
Dear God.
What did he say?
He said that there
is a management group.
What has the management team. Group
management team that is overall?
Have to learn it.
I can not sleep.
And I feel a little cold.
Have a seat ago Some homes.
Good food, warm clothing.
Obviously she is not
safe if you get out of here.
What do I need
to know about you?
My father, he
once working with John.
When this city there
is a safe place.
Invariably you?
First of all this.
But this is not anything.
He will not go anywhere.
He'll be here with you.
I talk to a doctor, just
for one moment, okay?
- Nadia, she alright?
- How did they find us.
They recognize me?
Not if I not in it.
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
He does not mind if I talk to
you for a moment he did not?
I'm here, Chi
town. She remembered me?
- Andrea, right?
- Yes.
We will talk for
a while, okay?
These guys were fighting in
the morning, these guys fight,
Who are we? Are
not the police?
I do not know.
It appears that they
have badges or something.
- Badges you?
- Yes.
Type badges yet right?
Hey, do not hurt him...
And she knows that
we want something not?
Toxin or
something in the hospital.
Someone took
toxin hospital stars?
All right.
- Thank you very much. Send her a drink.
- Thank you brother.
Next time I will find
her. Many thanks to her.
We go.
Hospital of St. Andrew
Security forces there.
How would you know?
They are not Ukrainians.
We have to track them.
I want you to follow them.
Not a problem.
No contact with some
other guy at all.
That guy can not
go anywhere far.
He is wanted something.
She worked in a bar.
Maybe we'll go back there.
For a team to go there
and Do not mess things up.
I'll go tell the boss.
Go there right away.
I'm there.
Be sure to catch her
live. The rest does not matter.
We now cause the wrong person.
I've seen her. I
was chasing them.
She can remember exactly
where She does not hide the camera?
Of course.
That's good because we will
not have time if back there.
I would worry that the two
boys, watch out for me, okay?
Let me know about girls.
Your mother Ching.
Tao Chi name. Not Ching.
So where is not polite.
Tao that bothered me
mad is very bright.
I'll pour boiling
water face it there.
- So we're working for someone?
- Your mother!
We I work for Mr. Chairman.
The boss? He
does all the guys?
It's what to expect from her?
You do not know.
I do not know whether
I New to ask you, idiot.
Soups and behold, it
looks better than that.
Sergei, I need your help.
I need two people to go
with me. Important story.
All right.
Have not found anything?
The boss. What
it means with you?
As far as I know, he is the overall
management of everything here.
These guys work for a
name called Mr. Chairman,
managing the entire region.
I need both of you over to me.
We will come to him. Where?
ONE goes to the club.
ONE club, you know?
Open bright spot that night.
I know, never closed.
We'll get there.
Money in two phases.
Follow me.
Stopping here goes.
Lowered his head away. We're
looking for you there.
- Nico, come meet me outside ONE.
- What happened?
We are here.
Take this party.
If something happens,
then her to run.
To me solve.
Okay, I have to go in there.
I will wait, go enlist.
- Is this place, huh?
- It is the place.
Throughout the night.
He checked the party
going, I will come to this side.
I want to start us off it.
Come on.
- Put them all on here.
- Well, I'll put them on.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm going to play. And you?
I walk.
Run away.
Run right away.
In all of this is
evidence to fight the monster.
The work he did with My
sister and another girl.
That's me in danger.
I'll handle this.
But first we need to find
a safe place for her.
He behold.
Come on, out the back door.
Your mother!
You talk too much.
Get out of here.
Getting you then, bastard.
Hurry go.
Clean away.
Come on. Come on.
Now we have to do?
We will follow them to their lair,
hang it on the new catch the tiger.
No, I do not have a
camera. But I did get a name.
Okay, I get it.
Yes sir.
Why do not you have
anything so surprised?
Actually, everything is
Where not too surprised.
All this I have thinking
for a long time.
Why, John? It may be
true that so anyway.
But you should
be careful to go.
Now you know too much.
And if I had to choose between me
and him surely I will choose me.
He knew that.
Okay, let's solve it goes.
Although we
generally do the job.
But they're much different.
A true warrior and a coward.
Coward is
always many also speak.
And with his mouth, then
perhaps gave him quite a lot.
And true warrior they
do not need those things.
They just everything must
conform to reason.
John, you do not need to involved
in this mess anywhere.
He could leave.
No damage at all.
Now hear me say this.
You know I hate someone
must solve.
Listen up,
everyone knows that
he without the camera.
I do not get it. You're no
longer interested in the camera anymore.
Everything simpler then.
Conversation between us there.
No need to follow
Where the hard way.
I do not care about the boss.
He thought he
could ensnare me?
There is one thing that
we or referred to in school.
If you play bad
others he must be careful.
Careful, now is his people
have to be careful.
There are people who go there.
Now hear me say this.
She will keep this one.
Listen and follow me. That's
how I solved it reassuring.
Keep going.
She should stay in the car. Do
not be out of the car if not me.
He has nothing to do huh Chi?
There was not anywhere
you wish, bald guy?
Then the other guy has
to say with him about me?
Are you sure you want
to hear the story there?
Shut it off.
Next time my reviews then
swipe up, assholes.
He is here.
She went over there
to go. He went with me.
That's because Sofia.
Bitch.
Boss will kill us now.
This is because of me.
We finished it.
He hit it, okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay, next time do
not adventure like that.
Probably do not
need to worry much.
Finding something?
His phone. He
wanted to see it?
Van Horn?
Not. Try again.
I'm waiting for the
phone of you there.
Ideally, then you should
return what belongs to me go.
I'm having a little problem...
to distinguish what is
of you or neither of you.
Maybe you should not be assigned
to the useless for this guy.
You should do what
that you want to do.
You do not want to others you
have to know the secret of it?
The secret is what?
Yeah, you do not have secrets.
Did you know that there is a
camera has returned to what you have done,
the bestial behavior
of the eyebrow.
What do you want?
I want to meet you.
Met.
Thus it easy to eat more.
Good for you and good for me.
Okay.
By ONE away, two hours.
You should be
prepared to go die.
Your mother, bastard.
John!
I have this thing for her.
This number will be enough
for her to start a new life.
Back to the family.
No!
I have no family to return.
I will not go anywhere.
So give me a hard right?
Chi, listen to me here.
He was wounded then. I need you
to take care of himself and her.
I'll handle this.
He did not get anywhere.
I'll be back soon.
Very punctual. Professional
Style. I like that.
The table sit with me right?
We met before.
So what you want?
I want to kill you.
Today you do not do that.
Tao is protected.
Now only socks still go.
You do not have
anything for me?
Maybe it belongs to you.
For that is what you did.
Kill him go.
What to say?
You solve this guy go.
You are Chi eh?
And you're a guy do?
The last guy you see.
You're just like that so?
Not bad.
I also do not
like that guy too.
Now I'm just alone with you.
Are you ready to die yet?
I died quite difficult.
I'm not playing anymore.
And those that
you pretty well.
By the time that
you were dead.
- You're out of ammo, then, bastard.
- Now what?
Solving such personal
things considered.
Stand up, stand up Review
to come, assholes.
Not use!
Why are you back?
I have to say I'm
not resolve that.
No need to say anything.
Thank you.
This is the last
thing I makes anyone.
This is the right
time for a new beginning.
I will have to follow
a different direction.
To start everything again.
And the Chi too, he
also needs a new start.